<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>
Computing Science News</title>
<link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/rss.xml</link><description>University of Aberdeen Computing Science Department news feed</description>
<language>en</language><copyright>Department Of Computing Science, University of Aberdeen</copyright>
<managingEditor>webmaster@csd.abdn.ac.uk</managingEditor>
<webMaster>webmaster@csd.abdn.ac.uk</webMaster>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 07:09:46 GMT</pubDate>
<image><url>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/images/rss_logo.jpg</url><title>University of Aberdeen Computing Science Dept.</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/rss.xml</link><width>144</width><height>31</height></image>
<item><title>Award from JISC-ENGAGE to Dr Peter Edwards for collaboration between Computing Science, the Macaulay Institute and Belfast eScience Centre. SwarmCloud project will explore deployment of a complex soci</title>
<description>Award from JISC-ENGAGE to Dr Peter Edwards for collaboration between Computing Science, the Macaulay Institute and Belfast eScience Centre. SwarmCloud project will explore deployment of a complex social simulation model into the eScience "Cloud" via the National Grid Service.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 08:17:42 GMT</pubDate>
<category>news</category>
</item><item><title>Vacancy - The Joking Computer (Closing Date 17|11|08).</title>
<description>The Joking Computer project builds on the results of the EPSRC-funded STANDUP project (http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/research/standup). The central aim is to create an interactive exhibit for use by children in public science centres; Glasgow Science Centre is a partner in this. Other activities include creation of an interactive website and the running of workshops for children.  (Closing Date: 17|11|08)</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 08:12:50 GMT</pubDate>
<category>general</category>
<link>http://www.abdn.ac.uk/jobs/display.php?recordid=YCS072R</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.abdn.ac.uk/jobs/display.php?recordid=YCS072R</guid></item><item><title>University's first grant under EPSRC Partnerships for Public Engagement scheme has been awarded to Dr Judith Masthoff and Dr Graeme Ritchie</title>
<description>The University of Aberdeen's first grant under the EPSRC Partnerships for
Public Engagement scheme has been awarded to Dr Judith Masthoff, to develop the
<a href="http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/research/standup">
STANDUP joke-generating software</a>
into an exhibit for science centres.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 09:48:44 GMT</pubDate>
<category>news</category>
<link>http://gow.epsrc.ac.uk/ViewGrant.aspx?GrantRef=EP/G020280/1</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">http://gow.epsrc.ac.uk/ViewGrant.aspx?GrantRef=EP/G020280/1</guid></item><item><title>MSc by Research Studentship with ITA</title>
<description>This research project, entitled "Proactive Agent Assistance for Military Missions", is funded by the US Army Research Laboratory, and the student will work within the International Technology Alliance (ITA) project teams based in the University of Aberdeen and Carnegie Mellon University, spending time both in Aberdeen and Pittsburgh during the period of the project. The MSc by Research studentship funding will pay fees (UK/EU level) and maintenance (&#163;12,940 tax free) for 12 months full time, and is available immediately.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 08:14:25 GMT</pubDate>
<category></category>
<link>ww.jobs.ac.uk/jobs/LT952/MSc_by_Research_Studentship/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">ww.jobs.ac.uk/jobs/LT952/MSc_by_Research_Studentship/</guid></item><item><title>CSD chair and committee membership for AAMAS</title>
<description>Wamberto Vasconcelos has been invited to be in the Senior Programme Committee of the 8th International Conference on Autonomous Agents and Multiagent Systems to be held in Budapest, Hungary, 10-15 May 2009. Tim Norman is to be Program Area Co-Chair</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 09:32:02 GMT</pubDate>
<category></category>
<link>http://www.conferences.hu/AAMAS2009/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.conferences.hu/AAMAS2009/</guid></item><item><title>High tech aids being developed to help tackle "care tsunami"</title>
<description>Dr. Ernesto Compatangelo is working with one of Scotland's largest charities to create intelligent software to help with the care of vulnerable people. Nick Baxter (CEO, Cornerstone) discusses these developments at the University's "Innovate with Aberdeen" event in Edinburgh.
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 11:20:37 GMT</pubDate>
<category>news</category>
<link>http://www.abdn.ac.uk/mediareleases/release.php?id=1240</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.abdn.ac.uk/mediareleases/release.php?id=1240</guid></item><item><title></title>
<description>Major research council award for Semantic Grid research at Aberdeen. <a href="http://www.policygrid.org/">PolicyGrid</a>  research node receives additional &#163;885K from ESRC to continue work until 2012.
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 11:16:17 GMT</pubDate>
<category>news</category>
<link>http://www.policygrid.org/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.policygrid.org/</guid></item><item><title></title>
<description>New EPSRC grant (joint with Dundee) on
   How was school today...?" - Supporting narrative for
   non-speaking children, a feasibility study
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 11:15:38 GMT</pubDate>
<category>news</category>
<link>http://howwasschooltoday.computing.dundee.ac.uk/</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">http://howwasschooltoday.computing.dundee.ac.uk/</guid></item><item><title>Free Laptop scheme for new Level 1 and Level 2 students</title>
<description>The University will provide a free laptop (value approx &#163;600) to all Home Fees Level 1 CS students commencing studies in September 2008. This scheme also applies to new Level 2 CS students joining in 2008.  The wireless laptop will have Windows XP installed, as well as Microsoft Office. It will also be pre-configured to use the University wireless cloud and e-mail. In addition, there will be some course specific content and software installed.
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 11:15:03 GMT</pubDate>
<category>news</category>
</item><item><title></title>
<description>David Corsar and Derek Sleeman have had a paper accepted for the high-profile academic Conference organized by the BCS, "Visions of Computer Science", to be held at Imperial College London on 22-24 September. Their paper is entitled: <em>Developing Knowledge-Based Systems using the Semantic Web</em></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 11:00:25 GMT</pubDate>
<category>news</category>
<link>http://bcs.org/server.php?show=ConWebDoc.20275</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">http://bcs.org/server.php?show=ConWebDoc.20275</guid></item><item><title>Half an issue of Artificial Intelligence filled with articles by departmental staff</title>
<description>Two of the four articles in the current (June 2008) issue of Artificial Intelligence are by CSD staff: Kees van Deemter and others, while another is by Chris Mellish and Jeff Pan.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 08:38:23 GMT</pubDate>
<category></category>
<link>http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/journal/00043702</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/journal/00043702</guid></item></channel></rss> 
