<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>K-CAP 07 News</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07</link><description>K-CAP 07 news feed</description><language>En</language><webMaster>dcorsar@csd.abdn.ac.uk</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2007 14:40:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Registration now open</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/registration.php</link><description>Registration for K-CAP 2007 is now open.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">{1aa01ed6-7460-ce0f-ca5f-1ede50a5b2ac}</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2007 14:40:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poster Submission Site Online</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/postersubmit.php</link><description>The poster submission site is now available; as are the instructions for how to submit your posters.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">{6587c3e8-da9d-c83f-2b2d-6aa3ffc29f55}</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2007 10:48:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Notification Delay</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07</link><description>We appologise to all those who submitted technical papers to K-CAP 2007.  Unfortunatly, there will be a slight delay in sending out notification of acceptance/rejection of technical papers: we now expect notifications to be sent out on Monday 25th June. </description><guid isPermaLink="false">{842f6354-e3af-2f6f-9f9e-d2742d79ad57}</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2007 16:57:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>K-CAP 2007 Call for Posters Released</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/cfposters.php</link><description>The call for posters for K-CAP 2007 is now available.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">{7b242a9f-72a6-b65-e27b-d722110e4dbf}</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2007 13:31:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Workshops Announced!</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/workshops.php</link><description>K-CAP 2007 will feature four workshops: "Knowledge Management and Semantic Web for Engineering Design", "Semantic Authoring, Annotation and Knowledge Markup", "Second International Workshop on Modular Ontologies", "Knowledge Capture and Constraint Programming".</description><guid isPermaLink="false">{53a16417-b347-431e-d638-1adea086bdeb}</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2007 14:05:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>K-CAP 2007 Technical Paper Submission site now open!</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/techpapersubmit.php</link><description>The submission site for technical papers is now open, please see http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/techpapersubmit.php for instructions</description><guid isPermaLink="false">{4880acd1-3926-de1a-3755-7119dc8ecb44}</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2007 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>K-CAP 2007 Submission Deadline for Workshop Proposals Postponed</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/cfw.php</link><description>The submission deadline for workshop proposals for K-CAP 2007 has been postponed until 20 April 2007, with notification of acceptance by 25 April 2007.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">{7a07b0d7-c129-b9af-d3f4-d6346d2183ba}</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 10:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>K-CAP 2007 Call for Workshops/Tutorials Released</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/cfw.php</link><description>The K-CAP 2007 Call for Workshops/Tutorials has been released and is available at http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/cfw.php</description><guid isPermaLink="false">{317431b5-db35-fa12-75fc-e107e05f506c}</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2007 15:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>K-CAP 2007 Call for Workshops/Tutorials</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/cfw.php</link><description>K-CAP 2007: Call for Workshop Proposals

The K-CAP 2007 Program Committee invites proposals for the Workshop Program for K-CAP 2007. Workshops will be held on Sunday, October 28th, the day before the regular conference technical sessions begin, at the conference hotel in Whistler, BC, Canada.

K-CAP workshops provide an informal setting where workshop participants have the opportunity to discuss specific technical topics in an atmosphere that fosters the active exchange of ideas. Our aim for the workshop program is to promote and collect multidisciplinary research directions that contribute to knowledge capture from a variety of sources. Members from all research areas related to knowledge capture are invited to submit workshop proposals. We particularly welcome workshops at discipline boundaries.

To encourage interaction and a broad exchange of ideas, each workshop will be limited to 30 participants and ample time will be allotted for general discussion.

Important Dates for Workshops

    * April 7, 2007: Proposal submission deadline
    * April 16, 2007: Acceptance notification
    * May 2, 2007: Publications of Workshops Call for Participation
    * (Individual workshops may set submission deadlines as they see fit)
    * Sept 10, 2007: Publication of K-CAP 2007 workshop program
    * October 1, 2007: Deadline for camera-ready workshop notes and other information
    * October 28, 2007: K-CAP 2007 workshops

Requirements for Submission

Proposals for workshops should be between two and five pages in length, and should contain the following information:

    * Contact information of the proposed workshop chair (name, department, university, telephone, fax and e-mail).
    * A brief technical description of the workshop, specifying the workshop goals and the technical issues that will be its focus.
    * A description of the workshop format, emphasizing how the format will encourage discussion.
    * A brief discussion of why and to whom the workshop is of interest.
    * A description of the qualifications of the individual committee members with respect to organizing the workshop, including a list of workshops previously arranged by any members of the proposed organizing committee, if any.
    * A list of potential participants, ideally with an indication of which participants have expressed an interest in attending the workshop.
    * A preliminary call for workshop papers. 

Timetable

All proposals should be submitted by electronic mail, to gennari@u.washington.edu, preferably in PDF (MS Word will also be accepted) by April 7, 2007.

Prospective organizers will be notified of the committee's decision no later than April 16, 2007. Each workshop organizing committee will be responsible for producing a Call for Participation for their workshop by May 2, 2007. By October 1, workshop organizing committees must provide any working notes to be duplicated for the workshops (up to a maximum of 150 pages), and a list of audio-visual requirements and any special room requirements.
K-CAP will be responsible for the following:

    * Providing publicity for the workshop series as a whole.
    * Providing logistics support and a meeting place for the workshop.
    * Duplicating working notes as described above and distributing them to the participants.

Please send your proposals and any inquiries to:

John Gennari, gennari@u.washington.edu.

Conference home page: http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/ </description><guid isPermaLink="false">{4e62eb92-48ae-c373-bbe3-c4cab9f3bd65}</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2007 15:23:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Technical Paper Submission Guidelines Released</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/techpaperguide.php</link><description>The guidelines for technical paper submissions has been released and is available at http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/techpaperguide.php</description><guid>{7674aab6-6b62-1256-aa21-566b660cf68f}</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2006 11:11:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>K-CAP 2007 Call for Papers</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/cfp.php</link><description>K-CAP 2007: Call for Papers
The Fourth International Conference on Knowledge Capture

28-31 October 2007, Whistler, BC
Website: http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/


Information in all forms is increasingly available, but using it effectively requires a range of technologies for acquiring and representing that information. These technologies constitute knowledge capture, and involve the extraction of useful knowledge from vast and diverse sources of information as well as its acquisition directly from users. Driven by the demands for knowledge-based applications and the unprecedented availability of information on the Internet, the study of knowledge capture has a renewed importance.  Although there has been considerable work in the area of knowledge capture, activities have been distributed across several distinct research communities, including knowledge engineering, machine learning, natural language processing, and the Semantic Web community. K-CAP 2007 will provide a forum that brings together disparate research communities such as these, whose members are interested in efficiently capturing knowledge from a variety of sources and in creating representations that can be useful for reasoning. We solicit high-quality research papers for publication and presentation at our conference. Our aim is to promote multidisciplinary research that could lead to a new generation of tools and methodologies for knowledge capture. K-CAP 2007 follows on the success of three previous conferences in 2005 (Banff, Canada), in 2003 (Florida, USA), and 2001 (Victoria, Canada).  The Fourth International Conference on Knowledge Capture, K-CAP 2007 will feature invited Talks, Technical Papers, Posters and Demos on a range of topics including:

   * Knowledge Engineering &amp; modelling methodologies
   * Knowledge Engineering &amp; the Semantic Web
   * Mixed-initiative planning &amp; decision-support tools
   * Acquisition of problem-solving knowledge
   * Knowledge-based markup techniques
   * Knowledge extraction systems
   * Knowledge acquisition tools
   * Advice taking systems

IMPORTANT DATES
Workshops / Tutorials proposals due	7 April 2007
Technical papers due                6 May 2007
Posters due                         1 July 2007
Workshops / Tutorials               28 October 2007
Conference                          29-31 October 2007

TECHNICAL PAPERS
Complete formatting instructions (including Microsoft Word and Latex templates) are available on the conference website. Briefly, submitted papers should be 8 pages, two columns, 10-point Times Roman (or equivalent), and "US letter" page-size. (Technical papers due 6 May 2007).


ABOUT THE VENUE
The conference will be held at The Fairmont Chateau Whistler (K-CAP 2007 has negotiated a Conference rate). Whistler is on the west side of the Rocky Mountains, and is easily reachable from Vancouver in less than 2 hours by road (~75 miles). Van services operate from Vancouver airport. Whistler is one of the sites of the 2010 Winter Olympics.

More information:
   * Whistler - http://www.whistler.ca/
   * Whistler.com - http://www.whistler.com/
   * Aloha Whistler - http://www.alohawhistler.com/whistler.php
   * The Fairmont Chateau Whistler - http://www.fairmont.com/whistler/
   * Vancouver airport - http://www.yvr.ca/
   * (Later the KCAP-07 www site will include information on travel)

K-CAP 2007 ORGANISING COMMITTEE  
Conference Chair            Derek Sleeman (University of Aberdeen)
Program Chair               Ken Barker (University of Texas)
Workshop &amp; Tutorials Chair  John Gennari (University of Washington)
Local Arrangements          Rob Kremer (University of Calgary)
Publicity                   Jeff Pan (University of Aberdeen)
Treasurer                   John Thompson (Boeing Company)
Sponsorship (Co-Chairs)     Yolanda Gil (USC) &amp; 
                            David Leake (Indiana University)
Webmaster                   David Corsar (University of Aberdeen)

K-CAP STEERING COMMITTEE
Peter Clark (Boeing Company)
Ken Forbus (Northwestern University)
Yolanda Gil (USC)
Rob Kremer (University of Calga</description><guid>{d223cb8a-3eef-ee92-7512-8ab4e7c0a4c4}</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2006 14:11:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Call for Papers Released</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/cfp.php</link><description>The Call for Papers has now been released.  Please see http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/cfp.php for details.</description><guid>{f880a05c-9bba-9649-ea16-24233ac5dd8c}</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2006 14:14:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>K-CAP 07 Flyer released</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/flyers/K-CAP-07-Flyer.pdf</link><description>The K-CAP 07 Flyer has been released.</description><guid>{68cafe31-5064-f4a7-29fb-4873e552b6c8}</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 14:21:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Submission dates released</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/dates.php</link><description>The K-CAP 07 submission dates have been released: they are as follows

Workshop/Tutorial proposals due 7th April 2007
Technical papers due 6th May 2007
Posters due 1 July 2007</description><guid>{2f37fb7b-d423-7bd2-4d97-21f861e9a623}</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 08:05:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Conference Dates and Location</title><link>http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/kcap07/dates.php</link><description>The dates of the conference have been decided.  They are as follows

Workshops: 28 Oct 2007
Conferencel: 29 - 31Oct 2007

Venue: The Fairmont Chateau, Whistler, BC</description><guid>{8466f459-24a3-75ea-fa71-ccbcf11a7d83}</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2006 13:14:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>